ultimatesocialplugin.com 2015-02-21

# Privacy Policy | GazMat

Website: http://ultimatesocialplugin.com

Company/Licensor: GazMat Publishing Ltd. (Under License)

Policy Effective From: 14 April 2013

Terminology Used

This is a privacy policy for the website listed above which from this point on will be referred to as ‘ _ **the website/we**_ ‘. belongs to /is licensed to the above listed company which from this point will be referred to as “ ** _the company_** ”. We may refer to you as ‘ _ **you/visitors/customers/users/guests**_ ****‘.

* * *

Purpose of the Policy

This policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide us & data obtained by automatic processes running on this _**website**_. By using the _**website**_ you accept the practices described in this document & you may also request for any such data to be disclosed to you or to be removed & how to go about it.

* * *

Data Privacy Disclaimer

The company does not store or collect any sensitive personal information that can lead to any financial loss or identity theft such as addresses, personal information, card details or account logins. All/any transactions are done on the payment aggregator’s own secure servers. Where payment is required the customer is redirected to their preferred payment gateway & then routed back once payment is complete.

* * *

Data Privacy & The Law

Your Data Privacy is protected under International Privacy Laws such as: UK Data Protection Act 1998, Privacy & Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 & the 1981 OECD Guidelines – you are entitled to ask for your data to be removed at no charge or for a report that details the data that we store about you for nominal admin fee of $10.

* * *

Personal Information We Collect

We are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of all our visitors. In the running of this _**website**_ we may collect the following data about you:

  1. Your Name & email address.
  2. Usage Info such as: pages views, geographic information and the resources that you access.
  3. Additional Information you provide when you communicate with us such as you IP Addresses, software you use.

* * *

Information We Track

We may if appropriate use cookies to gain information about the way you use this _**website**_ by means of tracking cookies.  
The ‘cookies’ are downloaded to your computer and stored on your hard drive – these only store information about your website usage & no personal data is stored there. This is normal practice & it only serves to help improve your visitor experience & for display of advertising that is relative to the content you have previously viewed.

You can at any time erase/decline these cookies by erasing the data from your hard drive. This is usually done by deleting your browsing history. The procedure for this is different for each browser so you must follow the instructions on how to do this from your preferred browsers website – simply search for ‘remove browsing history in “your browser name” for more information.

Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website. The procedure to remove these is the same as above.

* * *

How We Use Your Information

We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you.  In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  1. To provide you information about other products that may be of interest to you.
  2. To inform you of any changes to our website, services or products.

If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.

* * *

Disclosing of Your Information to Others

We won’t disclose your personal information to any other party other than in exceptional circumstances detailed below:

  1. In the event that we sell any or all of our business
  2. Where we are legally required by law.
  3. Where we use a third party to help protect your data

* * *

Adverts & Outbound Links

The _**website**_ may on occasion host advertisements or links to other websites – the _**company**_ is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such sites or in any way endorses their conduct. It’s the responsibility of the user to examine the practices & policies of any third party sites.

* * *

Contacting Us

Please don’t hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy using the contact form/details or support link provided on this _**website**_ ****.

* * *
